A Finding Aid to the James Graham & Sons Gallery Records, 1815, 1821, circa 1896-2011, bulk 1950s-1980s, in the Archives of American Art AAA.jamegras
Archives of American Art
- Printed Materials, 1949-2006; 1821; 1815; Series 8; 2.1 Linear feet Boxes 81-82, 97
  - Bulletins, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, Duveen-Graham Gallery, Exhibition Reviews and Catalogs, 1955-1958 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, Graham Gallery, 1958-1988 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Directory, The National Antique and Art Dealers Association of America, 1996 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Exhibition Announcements, Other Galleries, 1996-1999; 1980 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, C&M Arts, 1997-1998 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, Other Galleries, circa 1960s-2006 (Box 81, Folder 12-14)
  - Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, Graham Gallery, 1815; 1821; 1949-1987 (Box 81, Folder 15-20)
    Oversized material housed in Box 97, Folder 2
  - Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, Graham Gallery, circa 1960s-2006 (Box 82, Folder 1-6)
  - Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, Graham Gallery Group Shows, 1960s (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Guide Books, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Journals, "Art Now: New York", 1970 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Magazines, 1956-1998 (Box 82, Folder 10-14)
    Oversized material housed in Box 97, Folder 3
  - Newspapers, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Posters and Exhibition Catalogs, Miscellaneous, 1955-1970 (Box 82, Folder 16-17)
  - Oversized Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, Graham Gallery, 1999; 1993; 1972 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Oversized material from Box 81, Folder 19 and Box 82, Folder 2
  - Oversized Magazine, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Oversized material from Box 82, Folder 14
- Scrapbooks, 1897-1990s; Series 9; 0.9 Linear feet Boxes 82, 98-100
  This series contains 7 scrapbooks. Four of the scrapbooks chronicle the gallery's advertising efforts from 1940-1968 and 1981-1986; one scrapbook contains photographs of an art fair; and two scrapbooks document the careers of artists, Guy Coheleach and Van Dearing Perrine. Materials housed in the scrapbooks include clippings, catalogs, photographs, and other printed materials.
  Scrapbooks are arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - [Advertising], 1940-1950 (Box 82, Folder 18)
    Oversized material housed in Box 98, Folder 1
  - Advertising (1951-1957), 1967-1968; 1941-1958 (Box 82, Folder 19)
    Oversized materials housed in Box 99, Folder 1
  - Advertising (1958-1968) (Box 82, Folder 20)
    Oversized materials housed in Box 99, Folder 2
  - Advertising, 1981-1986 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - [Art Fairs, Graham Modern], circa 1980s-1990s (Box 82, Folder 22)
    Oversized material housed in Box 98, Folder 2
  - Coheleach, Guy, 1967-1972 (Box 82, Folder 23)
    Oversized material housed in Box 100, Folder 1
  - Perrine, Van Dearing, 1897-1965 (Box 82, Folder 24)
    Oversized material housed in Box 100, Folder 2
  - Oversized Scrapbook, [Advertising], 1940-1950 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    Oversized material from Box 82, Folder 18
  - Oversized Photographs Scrapbook, [Art Fairs, Graham Modern], circa 1980s-1990s (Box 98, Folder 2)
    Oversized material from Box 82, Folder 22
  - Oversized Scrapbook, Advertising (1951-1957), 1967-1968; 1941-1958 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    Oversized material from Box 82, Folder 19
  - Oversized Scrapbook, Advertising (1958-1968) (Box 99, Folder 2)
    Oversized material from Box 82, Folder 20
  - Oversized Scrapbook, Coheleach, Guy, 1967-1972 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Oversized material from Box 82, Folder 23
  - Oversized Scrapbook, Perrine, Van Dearing, 1897-1965 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    Oversized material from Box 82, Folder 24
- Photographic Materials, 1929-1990s; Series 10; 11.5 Linear feet Boxes 83-93, 96, 100-101
  Photographic Materials includes mostly black and white photographs, negatives, slides and transparencies of artwork; scattered photographs of installations, artists, and the gallery; and a handful of personal snapshots. The bulk of the photographs are undated, but were likely printed between 1950s-1990s.
  The photographs of artwork frequently include descriptive information on the back, including title, date of painting, dimensions, inventory number, price (sometimes in code), sold date, buyer name, and photographer's contact information. Also found are a few disassembled binders of collated photographs, and scattered exhibition catalogs, price lists, artists' biographies, and newspaper clippings interfiled with the photographs. Additional photographs are found in Artists' Files, following the original arrangement.
  Folders are filed alphabetically by artist's last name or subject, followed by unidentified photographs and photographs of artwork by various artists. Photographs of Seymour Fogel's artwork, exhibitions, and installations, as well as one folder of negatives related to Charlie Dye are filed at the end of this series and requires written permission of the donor in order to access (Boxes 93 and 101).
  - A, General, undated (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - A-B, Miscellaneous European or Non-American Sold, undated; 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Abstract Painters, 1952-1956 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - African, undated; circa late 1950s (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - American Landscapes, undated (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - American Still Life, undated (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Andre, Albert, undated (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Animals, 1955; undated; 1953 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Animals and Birds, undated; 1966; 1970 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Animals in Sculpture (from Pauline DiBlasi Studio), circa 1987 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Anshutz, Thomas P., undated (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - B, General, undated; circa late 1950s (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Baron, T., circa 1981 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Bellows, George, undated (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Bensley [Beasley?], undated (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Benton, Thomas Hart, 1965; undated (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Bierstadt, Albert, undated (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Bingham, George Caleb, circa 1961; undated (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Birch, Thomas, undated (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Bluemner, Oscar, undated (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Boggs, Frank, undated (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Boschaert, A., undated (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Bourdelle, Antoine, undated; 1962 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Boydell & Ravenet, circa after 1961 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Bradford, William, undated (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - Braught, Ross, undated (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Bronze Sculptures, circa mid-1980s (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - Bronzes, Bayre, Antoine-Louis, 1951; undated (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Bronzes, Mestrovic, Ivan, 1954-1956 (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - [Bronzes, Miscellaneous Photographic Materials], circa 1960s-1980s (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - [Bronzes, Miscellaneous Polaroids], circa 1960s-1980s (Box 83, Folder 31-32)
  - Bronzes, Rodin, Auguste, circa late 1950s (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Brown, James G., undated (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Bruce, Patrick, undated (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Brush, George de Forest, undated (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Buchser, Frank, undated (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Buttersworth, J.E., undated (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - C, General, undated (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - C, European or Non-American Sold, undated (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Calder, Alexander and Martin J. Heade, undated (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Calfee, William H., 1959; undated (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Callery, Mary, circa late 1950s (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Carsman, Jon, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 84, Folder 12-13)
  - Cassatt, Mary, undated (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Chabor, Moura, circa late 1950s (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Chase, William Merritt, undated (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Chierici, Gaetano, undated (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - China, Pottery, Porcelain, Silver and Miscellaneous Items, undated (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Coheleach, Guy, undated (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Constable, John, undated (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Cope, George, undated; circa 1959 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Copley, John S., undated (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Cropsey, J.F., undated (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - D, General, undated (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - D, Miscellaneous European or Non-American Sold, undated (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Da Silva, Joao, "Full Length of a Woman in Evening Dress", undated (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Dalen, Anton van, undated (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Daubigny, Charles F., undated (Box 84, Folder 28)
  - Davies, Arthur B., undated (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - Dawson, Montague, undated (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - De Kooning, Elaine, undated; circa mid-1950s-1981 (Box 84, Folder 31-35)
  - De Kooning, Elaine, JFK Portrait, 1964 (Box 84, Folder 36)
  - De Kooning, Elaine, Versus President Kennedy, 1959-1964 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Demuth, Charles, undated (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - D'Espagnet, George, circa late 1950s (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Dewing, T.W., undated (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Dole, William, circa late 1950s-1960; undated (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Doughty, Thomas, undated (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Draper, William F. (Box 85)
    - Doctors' Portraits, undated; 1960s (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Exhibition (Oct. 23 - Nov. 17, 1973), circa 1973 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Installation of Show (1971), undated (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Landscapes, circa 1966-1973; undated (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Portraits, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Dunlap, William, undated (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Durand, Asher B., undated (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - E, General, undated; 1956 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Eakins, Thomas, undated (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Early American Portraits, undated (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - East Indian Art, undated (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Eastman, Seth, undated (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Edmunds, Francis W., undated (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - European, A-W, undated; circa 1950s-1980s (Box 85, Folder 20-39)
  - European Genre, 1953; undated (Box 85, Folder 40)
  - European Landscapes, undated (Box 85, Folder 41)
  - European Portraits, undated (Box 85, Folder 42)
  - European Still Life, undated (Box 85, Folder 43)
  - F, General, undated (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - F-G, Miscellaneous European or Non-American, undated (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Fine, Perle, 1967; undated (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Flemish, "Purgatory" (?), undated (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Francis, J.F., undated (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Fulbright Exhibition, circa late 1950s (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Fuller, George, undated (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - G, General, undated (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Gainsborough, Thomas, undated (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Gallery Photographs, circa 1966-1967 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Gamble, Edwin, circa 1960s (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Gérôme, Jean-Leon, undated (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Gérôme, Jean-Leon, Sold, undated (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Glackens, William, undated (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Gladstone, Gerald, circa 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Glarner, Fritz, circa late 1950s-1968; undated (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Glasier, M., 1962; undated (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Glintenkamp, Henry J., undated (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Goodwin, R. La Barre, undated (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Graham Gallery (October 1973), undated (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - [Graham, Robert, Personal], circa 1970s-1980s (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Granville-Smith, Walter, "In the Surf", undated (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - Granville-Smith, Walter, Sold, undated (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - Greenwood, John, undated (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - H, General, undated; circa late 1950s (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - H, Miscellaneous European or Non-American Sold, undated (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - Hagborg, August, undated (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - Hague, Raoul, undated (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - Hancock, Theodore, undated (Box 86, Folder 29)
  - Harding, Chester, undated (Box 86, Folder 30)
  - Harnett, William, undated (Box 86, Folder 31)
  - Harvey, James, undated; 1964; 1958 (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - Harvey, James, Slides of Paintings, 1959-1962 (Box 86, Folder 33)
  - Hassam, Childe, undated (Box 86, Folder 34)
  - Heade, Martin J., undated (Box 86, Folder 35)
  - Heidenreich, Carl, undated (Box 86, Folder 36)
  - Henri, Robert, undated; 1963 (Box 86, Folder 37)
  - Henry, E.L., undated (Box 86, Folder 38)
  - Hensley, Jackson, undated (Box 86, Folder 39)
  - Hesselius, John, undated (Box 86, Folder 40)
  - H.M.S. London, 1957; undated (Box 86, Folder 41)
  - Holden, Norman, 1964; undated (Box 86, Folder 42)
  - Homer, Winslow, undated (Box 86, Folder 43)
  - I, General, 1955; undated (Box 86, Folder 44)
  - Indian Photos, 1953; 1961; undated (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Inness, George, undated (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Installation of Japanese Group Show?, undated (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Italian School 17th Century, 1954; undated (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - J, General, undated (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - J, Miscellaneous European or Non-American Sold, undated (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Jenkins, G.W., undated (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Jensen, Alfred, undated; 1963 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - John, Augustus, undated (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Johnson, Eastman, undated (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - K, General, undated (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - K, Miscellaneous Non-American Sold, undated (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Kadish, Reuben, undated; 1964 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Kensett, J.F., undated (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Kilburne, Goodwin, undated (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - King, Charles Bird, undated (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Kolle, Helmut, circa late 1950s (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Koplin, Norma Jean, undated (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Krieghoff, Cornelius, undated (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - L, General, undated (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - L, Miscellaneous Non-American Sold, undated (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - La Farge, John, undated (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - Lambdin, James R., undated (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - Lawson, Ernest, undated (Box 87, Folder 24)
  - Lettick, Birney, undated (Box 87, Folder 25)
  - Loran, Erle, circa 1963; undated (Box 87, Folder 26)
  - Luce, Maximilien, undated (Box 87, Folder 27)
  - Luks, George, undated (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - M, General, circa late 1950s; undated (Box 87, Folder 29)
  - M, Miscellaneous Non-American Sold, undated (Box 87, Folder 30)
  - Malicoat, Philip, undated (Box 87, Folder 31)
  - Marlow, William, undated (Box 87, Folder 32)
  - Martin, Homer D., undated (Box 87, Folder 33)
  - Maufra, undated (Box 87, Folder 34)
  - McCall, Charles, undated (Box 87, Folder 35)
  - Mills, I.H., From Courbet Autograph Book, undated (Box 87, Folder 36)
  - Minelli, Giovanni, "Portrait of a Roman Emperor", undated (Box 87, Folder 37)
  - Miniatures, undated; 2 Folders (Box 87, Folder 38-39)
  - Miyashita, Tad, undated (Box 87, Folder 40)
  - Moran, Thomas, undated (Box 87, Folder 41)
  - Moret, Henry, undated (Box 87, Folder 42)
  - Morse, Samuel F.B., undated (Box 87, Folder 43)
  - Mount, William, undated (Box 87, Folder 44)
  - Munson, D., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 45)
  - Murphy, Stanley, undated (Box 87, Folder 46)
  - N, General, undated (Box 87, Folder 47)
  - N, Miscellaneous Non-American Sold, undated (Box 87, Folder 48)
  - National Gallery of Scotland [Slides], circa late 1970s-1984 (Box 87, Folder 49)
  - Neagle, John, undated (Box 87, Folder 50)
  - Neel, Alice, 1974; undated (Box 87, Folder 51)
  - Neel, Alice, 1980; undated (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Negret, Edgar, 1960s (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Nelson, Dianne, circa 1968-1975; undated (Box 88, Folder 3-4)
  - Netsukes, undated (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - O, General, undated (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - O, Miscellaneous Non-American Sold, undated (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Oberteuffer, George, undated (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Objects (Box 88)
    - Arms and Armor, undated (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Boxes - Watches (Musical - Mechanical), undated (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Bronzes, Not In Stock, 1946; circa late 1950s; undated (Box 88, Folder 11-13)
    - Ivories, undated; 1936 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, undated; 1962 (Box 88, Folder 15-16)
    - [Netsukes?], undated (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Pistols and Guns, 1940; undated (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Silver, American, 1954; undated (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Objects (Box 89)
    - Silver, American, 1936-1960s; undated (Box 89, Folder 1-3)
    - Silver, English and Modern, undated (Box 89, Folder 4-7)
    - Tankards, Porringers, Coffee and Teapots, undated (Box 89, Folder 8-10)
  - Osthaus, Edmund, undated (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Otis, Bass, undated (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - P, General, undated; 1957 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - P, Miscellaneous Non-American Sold, undated (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Pace, Stephen, circa 1969 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Peale, Charles Willson, undated; 1946 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Peale, James, undated (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Peale, Raphaelle and Titian, undated (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - Peale, Rembrandt, 1946; undated (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - Peale Women, undated (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - Peckstein, "Interior View" Consignment, undated (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - Photographs Listed Alphabetically (A-G) - Unused, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - Photographs Listed Alphabetically (N-Z), circa 1950s-1970s (Box 89, Folder 23-25)
  - Photographs Listed Alphabetically (N-Z), circa 1970s (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - [Photographs Listed Alphabetically] N-Z, Sold Paintings, circa 1950s-1970s (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Polk, Charles Peale, undated (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Pollock, Jackson, undated (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Potthast, Edward, undated (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Prendergast, Maurice, 1960; undated (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Puvis de Chavannes, Pierre, undated (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Pyle, Howard, undated (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Q, General, undated (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - R, General, undated (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - R, Miscellaneous Non-American Sold, undated (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Ramirez, Eduardo, 1960s; undated (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Red Clay Sculptures, circa mid-1980s-1990s (Box 90, Folder 13-19)
  - Reid, Robert, undated (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Renninger, Katherine, circa late 1950s (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - Richardt, F., undated (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - Riemenschneider, Tillman, "St. Nicholas of Bari", undated (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - Rimmer, William, undated; circa late 1950s (Box 90, Folder 24)
  - Robins, Louisa, circa late 1950s (Box 90, Folder 25)
  - Robinson, Theodore, undated (Box 90, Folder 26)
  - Roesen, Severin, undated (Box 90, Folder 27)
  - Roesen, Severin, "Still Life - Fruit", undated (Box 90, Folder 28)
  - Roman II Century, "Marble Statue of a Faun", undated (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Rungius, Carl, undated (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Russell, Alfred, circa late 1950s (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - Russell, Warren, undated (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Ryder, 1963 (Box 90, Folder 33)
  - S, General, undated (Box 90, Folder 34)
  - S, Miscellaneous Non-American Sold, undated (Box 90, Folder 35)
  - Sargent, John Singer, undated (Box 90, Folder 36)
  - Schacter, F., undated (Box 90, Folder 37)
  - Scriver, Bob, "Rodeo Series", circa 1980-1987 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Sharples, James, undated (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Shaw, Joshua, undated (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Shinn, Everett, 1952; undated (Box 91, Folder 4-5)
  - Slamm, Roy Alan, 1965-1966 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Slivka, David, undated (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Sloan, John, circa 1965 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Stein, Walter, undated (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Sterling, James, circa 1964 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Stuart, Gilbert, undated (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Stull, Henry, undated (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Sully, Thomas, undated (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Suzuki, James, undated; 1957; circa 1961 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Swinden, Albert, undated (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Syeppa, Joseph, undated (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - T, General, undated (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - T, Miscellaneous Non-American Sold, undated (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Tait, A.F., undated (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Terris, Albert, undated; circa late 1950s (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Tiffany & Co., "Bronze Gilt Candle Stand", undated (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Tobias, Alan, undated (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - Toshio [Exhibition Catalog], 1959 (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - Touster, Irwin, circa 1970s (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Tracy, J.M., undated (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - Twachtman, John Henry, undated (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - U, General, undated (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - U-V, Miscellaneous Non-American Sold, undated (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - Utley, Windsor, undated (Box 91, Folder 29)
  - V, General, undated (Box 91, Folder 30)
  - Valledor, Leo, undated (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Valtat, Louis, 1952; undated (Box 91, Folder 32)
  - Vander Sluis, George, circa late 1950s; undated (Box 91, Folder 33)
  - Vanderlyn, John, undated (Box 91, Folder 34)
  - Vera, Ramon, circa late 1950s (Box 91, Folder 35)
  - Villon, Jacques, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 36)
  - Vittoria, Alessandro, "Bronze - JOVE", undated (Box 91, Folder 37)
  - Vivone, Linda, circa 1968-1970 (Box 91, Folder 38)
  - Vlaminck, Maurice de, undated (Box 91, Folder 39)
  - Von Schlegell, William, 1952 (Box 91, Folder 40)
  - Vonnoh, Robert, undated (Box 91, Folder 41)
  - W, General, undated (Box 91, Folder 42)
  - W, Miscellaneous Non-American Sold, undated (Box 91, Folder 43)
  - Walton, William, undated; 1967 (Box 91, Folder 44)
  - Waugh, Frederick J., undated (Box 91, Folder 45)
  - Weinman, Adolf Alexander, "Chief Black Bird", 1958 (Box 91, Folder 46)
    Oversized material housed in Box 100, Folder 3
  - Weir, J. Alden, undated (Box 91, Folder 47)
  - West, Benjamin, undated (Box 91, Folder 48)
  - Western Artwork, undated; 1944; 1929 (Box 91, Folder 49)
  - Western Artwork, undated; 1977; 1957; 1929 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Western Miscellaneous, undated; 1955 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Whistler, James A. McNeill, undated (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - White, Robert, circa 1960s-1990s (Box 92, Folder 4-5)
  - Whittredge, Worthington, undated (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Wilmarth, Christopher, circa 1967-1968 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Wyeth, Andrew, undated (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Wyeth, N.C., 1964; undated (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - X-Z, General, undated (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Z, Miscellaneous Non-American, undated (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Zerega, Andrea Pietro, undated (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Unidentified Artwork, undated; 1953; circa 1970s-1980s (Box 92, Folder 13-14)
  - Unidentified Artwork [Seymour Fogel?], circa 1950s-1970s (Box 92, Folder 15)
    Oversized materials housed in Box 96, Folders 6-9
  - Unidentified Artwork [Murillo, "La Anunciacion"?], circa 1983 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Unidentified Artwork, Slides [Mario Yrisarry?], circa 1960s (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Various Artists, circa 1950s-1991; undated (Box 92, Folder 18-24)
  - Various Artists [Francis Celentano, Roy Colmer, John Hebeler, Jay Rosenblum, Donald Yacoe], 1967-1968 (Box 92, Folder 25)
  - Various Artists [James Peale, Raphaelle Peale, Sarah Peale, Fritz Glarner, Walter Stein and others], circa 1979-1984 (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - Various Artists, Slides [Dessner (1968), Jensen, Kruskenick (1964), James Suzuki (1967), Zacharias (1968)], circa 1964-1968 (Box 92, Folder 27)
    Materials housed in a shoebox in Box 100, Folder 4
  - Various Artists, Transparencies, circa 1990s (Box 92, Folder 28)
  - Various Artists, Transparencies, From Guild Hall, circa 1990s (Box 92, Folder 29)
  - Dye, Charles, Color Negatives, undated (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Fogel, Seymour (Box 93)
    - Artist's Binder, circa 1960s (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Bellevue Hospital, NYC (1973), circa 1970s (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Brooklyn-Methodist Hospital (1958), circa 1950s (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Executed Safford, AZ, circa 1940s-1970s (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Exhibitions, circa 1950s-1970s (Box 93, Folder 6)
      Oversized materials housed in Box 101, Folder 2
    - First Christian Church of Houston, TX, Facade Glazed Brick and Stained Glass (1956), circa 1950s (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Foley Square U.S. Custom Ct. Bldg. Mosaic, NYC (1968), circa 1960s-1970s (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Fort Worth Federal Building (1966), circa 1960s-1970s (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Gouverneur Hospital Lobby Mural, NYC (1971-?), circa 1970s (Box 93, Folder 10)